xodo.com 2015-11-06

# 

XODO                                               XODO TECHNOLOGIES INC.
                                                              (“Xodo”)
                                                         PRIVACY POLICY
1.        Our Commitment to Privacy.                     Xodo respects your right to personal privacy. Xodo’s Privacy Policy is
intended to comply with the British Columbia Personal Information Protection Act. Xodo expects to regularly review its privacy
policies and practices. We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy at any time. Notice that changes to our
Privacy Policy have been made will be indicated on the Policy the date it was last updated.
2.        Personal Information.                 “Personal information” is personally identifiable information such as your name,
residential address, and e-mail address or any other information that can be used to identify an, or about an identifiable,
individual. Personal information is collected by Xodo when you provide it to us, such as if you choose to register with us after
downloading our Xodo software application offered on Apple Corporation’s iTunes Application Store web site, Microsoft
Corporation’s Windows Phone Apps and Game Store, or Google Inc.’s Play Store web site (our “software”) or if you visit our
web site and choose to provide us with details about yourself, including your name, mailing address, and email address to
participate in any services we may offer.
3.        Collection, Use and Storage of Personal Information.              Xodo collects and uses your personal information if
and when you register with us, to enable you to use our software’s functionality with the related services on our web site. We
also collect personal information to allow us to keep you informed on our latest software announcements and software
updates. Xodo may also collect certain personal information when you use our web site or services, such as the name of the
internet service provider and the Internet Protocol address through which you access the Internet; the time you access our web
site; and the pages that are accessed at our web site.
Xodo uses this information to help us develop, deliver, and improve our services. Xodo may also contact you from time to time
to conduct market research and surveys in an effort to continually improve our products and services.
4.        Non-Personal Information.             Xodo also collects non-personally identifiable information about you in a number
of ways, including tracking your activities through your IP address, computer settings, or keywords used which let us know
which aspects of our software you prefer using. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personally identifiable
information for any purpose.
We may collect information such as your occupation, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, location, and the
time zone where our software is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our services. If we
combine non-personally identifiable information with personal information, the combined information will be treated by us as
personal information for so long as it remains combined.
5.        Release of Personal Information.               Unless you specifically authorize Xodo to release your personal
information, or release is required or permitted by law, Xodo will not sell, lease, or trade your personal information to other third
parties. Personal information collected by Xodo is processed and stored in Canada and such personal information may be
subject to disclosure in accordance with the laws applicable in such jurisdiction. These laws may not provide the same level of
protection for personal information as do the applicable laws of the jurisdiction in which you ordinarily reside. Anonymous or
“non-personal” information gathered by Xodo through your use of our software, web site, or our services may be used for
technical, research, and analytical purposes. Information collected through surveys may be used by Xodo to analyze our
services, target market, and to develop or enhance our services. If Xodo is involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of
sale of some or all of its assets, we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party. Xodo
reserves the right to use, disclose, sell, rent, or trade aggregated, non-personally identifiable data provided that such data is
not linked to any specific individual.
6.        Informed Consent.                     Xodo will only ask for personal information about you that Xodo needs and will
only ask for it when it is needed. When Xodo asks you for the information, Xodo will explain to you why such information is
needed and what Xodo is going to do with it. Xodo will seek your prior consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of the
information as required by applicable privacy legislation.
7.        Use of Cookies.              Xodo’s web site, and software technology may use “cookies” to collect information
anonymously, helping Xodo understand user behaviour and preferences. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a storage
device by a web site. “Cookies” contain a unique identification number that identifies your browser, but not you, to our
computers each time you visit our web site or use certain features of our software. Xodo treats information collected by cookies
as non-personally identifiable information.
8.        Accuracy.          If you have questions about the accuracy of factual information about you, you will have access to
that information in order to verify and update it.

9.        Security.          Our web site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and
alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, Xodo will take
all reasonable steps to ensure the safety of your personal information.
10.       Links to Other Web Sites.           Our web site contains links to other web sites. Xodo is not responsible for the
privacy practices or the content of such other web sites and expressly disclaims all liability associated with your use of and the
content of such other sites.
11.       Non-Canadian Residents.             Personal information collected by Xodo in connection with this Agreement will be
stored and processed in Canada.
12.       Revisions to this Privacy Policy.             Xodo expects to revise this Privacy Policy from time to time, reflecting
changes in its technology, customer feedback, and applicable legislation. Please ensure that you refer to the current version of
our Privacy Policy.
13.       Withdrawing Consent.                Except as required by law, Xodo will not use or disclose your personal
information for any purpose for which you refuse us consent or later withdraw your consent. If you withdraw consent, you agree
that in spite of this withdrawal we may continue to use the personal information previously provided to us to the extent that we
are contractually obligated to do so and to the extent necessary to enforce any contractual obligations you may have to Xodo.
You also understand that although you can use our software for some purposes without providing us with any personal
information, we need personal information about you for some functionality, including particulars that may require payment or
involve an ongoing relationship with Xodo. If you refuse to provide us with the information we require or later withdraw your
consent to use and disclose this information, we may no longer be able to provide you with these services.
Last updated: January 14, 2014
                                                                                                                                  2
